export const dummyStackData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    front: "United States of America",
    back: "Washington, D.C.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    front: "Canada",
    back: "Ottawa",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    front: "Japan",
    back: "Tokyo",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    front: "United Kingdom",
    back: "London",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    front: "France",
    back: "Paris",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    front: "Germany",
    back: "Berlin",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    front: "Italy",
    back: "Rome",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    front: "Spain",
    back: "Madrid",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    front: "Australia",
    back: "Canberra",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    front: "Brazil",
    back: "Brasilia",
  },
];
